Last year the smoking tire went on the Bull Run live rally in the 2010 Ford SVT Raptor.
I liked it so much, I bought one, and here it is.
We're going back to Bull Run this year, of course, to help from our friends at Black Magic,
and we're so serious about it, we got two Valentine 1 radar detectors.
Oh yeah.
So we're all set up, and the reason we got two is because we're going to be going a little bit faster.
We got a 2011 Shelby GT500 with a 550 horsepower all aluminum V8.
We are going to be right in the action bringing you guys a video every single day,
live from the Bull Run rally, July 9th to 16th.
And the only place to watch it is on BlackMagicshine.com, or right here on the Smoking Tire.